Finding Aid for the John V. Van Sickle Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
John V. Van Sickle Collection
1942-1946
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0465
.01 linear_feet
Scope aod Contents
This collection contains six journal articles and two publications, all in pamphlet form. Professor Van Sickle was in the Economics Department.
- Journal Articles
  - Geographical Aspects of a Minimum Wage reprinted from Harvard Business Review, 1946 Spring
  - Has Private Enterprise a Future? reprinted from The Journal of Capital Management, 1944 May
  - The International Labor Office: An Appraisal reprinted from The Southern Economic Journal, 1946 April
  - Reform of Federal Taxes on Personal and Corporate Income reprinted from American Economic Review, 1944 December
  - Regional Aspects of the Problem of Full Employment at Fair Wages reprinted from The Southern Economic Journal, 1946 July
  - Regionalism: A Tool of Economic Analysis reprinted from American Economic Review, 1945 May
- Publications
  - Public Works, Economic Stabilization, and the Rural South (Papers of the Institute of Research and Training in Social Sciences – Number Two) published by Vanderbilt University Press, Tennessee, 1942 January
  - The Stake of the Cotton South in International Trade published by University of California Press, California, 1945